twitrounds.com 2011-10-05

# Privacy Policy | Twitter Backgrounds

**General**  
This privacy policy covers how twitrounds.com treats personal information that is collected and/or used throughout the site. twitrounds does not intend to collect any personal information from children under 13 unless we believe such collection to be permitted by law. twitrounds believes respects the privacy of our visitors.

**Use of information** :  
twitrounds does not store any personal information. twitrounds does in fact use 3rd party ad servers and tracking systems to better understand visitor patterns allowing twitrounds to create quality content that is desired by future visitors. twitrounds will never use any of this information in any harmful way or directly share this information with any agencies looking to invade your privacy.

twitrounds uses companies such as Google, ValueClickMedia, CPX Interactive, among others,  to serve the advertisements on some of our pages. These companies and advertisers may place and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. We may use your information or allow advertisers or companies that serve advertisements access to your information to determine which advertisements you will see. This information may include your demographic information, geographic location, what content you access on our site, how you rate various content, language contained in your comments and other information.

**Storing of information** :  
Throughout the site, twitrounds will ask for twitter usernames and passwords. This information is never stored and saved on twitrounds server. This information is used on a one time basis to allow visitors to efficiently upload their prefered background to their profile. If users are uncomfortable entering this information, twitrounds does provide steps to manually install backgrounds. twitrounds will not be held liable for mis-use of our automatic install process.

****Binding Agreement**** **:**  
Your use of twitrounds, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By using our Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. twitrounds is not held liable for any incorrect statements made in this Privacy Policy and will attempt to correct any mistakes upon discovery.
